<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClujApp</string>

    <!--Attractions Names -->
    <string name="banffy">Banffy Castle</string>
    <string name="ethnography_museum">Ethnography Museum</string>
    <string name="dormition">Dormition Cathedral</string>
    <string name="matthias">Matthias Monument</string>


    <!--Attractions Descriptions -->
    <string name="banffy_desc">Bánffy Castle is an architectural monument situated in Bonţida, a village in the vicinity of Cluj-Napoca, Romania, with construction phases and stylistic features belonging to Renaissance, Baroque, Neoclassical and Neogothic styles."</string>
    <string name="ethnography_museum_desc">The Transylvanian Museum of Ethnography is situated in Cluj-Napoca, Romania. With a history of more than 80 years, the Ethnographic Museum of Transylvania is one of the first and greatest of its kind in Romania</string>
    <string name="dormition_desc">The Dormition of the Theotokos Cathedral is the most famous Romanian Orthodox church of Cluj-Napoca, Romania.</string>
    <string name="matthias_desc">The Matthias Corvinus Monument is a monument in Cluj-Napoca, Romania. This classified historic monument, conceived by János Fadrusz and opened in 1902 </string>

    <!-- Festivals Life -->
    <string name="electric_castle">Electric Castle</string>
    <string name="untold">Untold</string>

    <!-- Festivals Descriptions -->
    <string name="electric_desc">ELECTRIC CASTLE is a Romanian music festival that takes place every year on the Transylvanian spectacular domain of Banffy Castle, near Cluj-Napoca.</string>
    <string name="untold_desc">Untold Festival is the largest annual electronic music festival held in Romania, taking place in Cluj-Napoca. Untold has been designated Best Major Festival within European Festival Awards 2015</string>
    <string name="price">Price:</string>
    <string name="attractions_tab_name">Attractions</string>
    <string name="festivals_tab_name">Festivals</string>
    <string name="food_tab_name">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="hotel_tab_name">Hotels</string>
    <string name="textView_place_description">Description</string>
    <string name="textView_place_name">Name</string>


    <!-- Hotels -->
    <string name="hotelcamino">Hotel Camino</string>
    <string name="grandhotelnapoca">Grand Hotel Napoca</string>
    <string name="westcityhotel">West City Hotel</string>

    <!-- Hotels Descriptions -->
    <string name="hotelcamino_desc">The Palace is dating from the 16th century.The restaurant is located in a Palace dating from the 16th century, which during the years was the residence of a very rich and respected family. Over time it changed many times its purpose, getting to be even a maternity.</string>
    <string name="grandhotelnapoca_desc">The Grand Hotel Napoca is located on the meandering Someşul Mic river bank, 250 m from Parcul Central. Customised tours of the city with a specialised guide are available to guests.</string>
    <string name="westcityhotel_desc">This 4-star design West City Hotel is 6 km from the centre of Cluj-Napoca near the Polus Shopping Centre. The non-smoking property offers free WiFi, free private parking and air-conditioned rooms with bathrobes and hairdryers.</string>



    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="baraccacluj">Baracca</string>
    <string name="roatarestaurant">Roata Restaurant</string>


    <!-- Restaurants Descriptions -->
    <string name="baraccacluj_desc">Design food. Located in downtown Cluj-Napoca, our restaurant is the place where architecture, design and passion for life</string>
    <string name="roatarestaurant_desc">The restaurant serves traditional romanian food. The menu is not too diverse, but the food is tasty. We had trout with potatoes, traditional cooked cabbage and chicken soup. We also received from the house some traditional drinks.</string>
</resources>
